<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Silvanna on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/silvanna.html</link><description>Recent content in Silvanna on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/silvanna/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>silvanna</title><link>/hero/silvanna.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/silvanna.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">SILVANNA HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/silvanna.jpg" title="SILVANNA HD Wallpaper" alt="SILVANNA HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> The prince has gone missing and no one knows if he&amp;#39;s dead or alive! For the sake of the country and the safety of its people, King Aurelius II has decreed to expand Knight&amp;#39;s Order and set up fortresses in the outskirts of Moniyan to reinforce the empire’s defense. In the meantime, Imperial Knights continue to search for any clue of the whereabouts of the prince. Imperial Knights search day and night. They have almost crossed the entire Land of Dawn but all they have found is endless waiting. The Aurelius royal family is drowning in sorrow. To young Silvanna, the tragic memory of that time is too heavy. As a princess, Silvanna has always had a heart of justice and compassion since she was little. After her brother&amp;#39;s disappearance, she has been keeping the queen company almost every day. For years, the two of them have been waiting for a miracle in the imperial castle. However, day after day, year after year the queen eventually becomes ill and bedridden from physical and mental exhaustion. &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>