<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ruby on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/ruby.html</link><description>Recent content in Ruby on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/ruby/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ruby</title><link>/hero/ruby.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/ruby.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">RUBY HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/ruby.jpg" title="RUBY HD Wallpaper" alt="RUBY HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> A long time ago, brave hunter grandpa saved Little Red Hood and her granny from the wolf&amp;#39;s belly and they lived happily ever after....though that was not how the real story ended. The wolf pack, harboring bitter resentment from this, never forgot the scars on the belly. One dark night when the moon was hidden, the new wolf king Haas led the pack and attacked the village in revenge, and elderly hunter grandpa was slained in an attempt to save granny. All of this happened before the eyes of Ruby, the Little Red Hood and drove this innocent girl into madness. With a scythe she sliced the wolf king into two pieces then peeled off its skin and swallowed its heart raw. Althought the happy memories with grandma and grandpa still vividly flash before her eyes, things would never be the same again. After burying her families, Ruby started to wander in the Land of Dawn carrying her scythe. She made a vow - that she would create a happy ending for every story. &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>