<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Angela on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/angela.html</link><description>Recent content in Angela on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/angela/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>angela</title><link>/hero/angela.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/angela.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">ANGELA HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/angela.jpg" title="ANGELA HD Wallpaper" alt="ANGELA HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> Dr. Baker was one of the founders of Lab 1718, an institution created with the aim of bringing peace to the world. But as his co-founders fell deeper and deeper into their depraved human weaponization experiments, Dr. Baker felt he had no choice but to leave and pursue a new project. Renouncing the questionable ethics of human experimentation, he endeavored to create a new kind of lifeform, solely from a mechanical skeleton, puppet strings, and synthetic skin, and finally, a new generation of artificial life was born. Dr. Baker firmly believed that love and hope were the greatest inventions of mankind, so he programmed the world&amp;#39;s most moving stories into the heart of his new creation. One bright morning, Peace Android Prototype 1 awakened from her bed, and Dr. Baker bestowed upon this adorable mechanical angel, the name Angela. Angela followed Dr. Baker&amp;#39;s tutelage, studying hard to understand the world, and hoping to meet the doctor&amp;#39;s high expectations. However, their peaceful life together was soon cut short. When the mad scientists of Lab 1718 heard rumors that Dr. Baker had created a living soul outside of a human body, they couldn&amp;#39;t believe it. They convinced themselves that Baker had betrayed them, keeping this knowledge to himself before fleeing, and so they ordered Dr. Baker&amp;#39;s past creations, Alpha and Beta to hunt down Dr. Baker and his creation. As their pursuers were just about to close in on them, Dr. Baker placed Angela into a flight capsule, instructing her to seek out his good friend Dr. Rooney. However, the flight capsule was struck down a terrible thunderstorm, and landed in a remote corner of the Land of Dawn. Emerging from the wreckage, Angela began her journey to find Dr. Rooney, and save her father. &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>