<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Atlas on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/atlas.html</link><description>Recent content in Atlas on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/atlas/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>atlas</title><link>/hero/atlas.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/atlas.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">ATLAS HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/atlas.jpg" title="ATLAS HD Wallpaper" alt="ATLAS HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> The dark, cold and mysterious deep sea is the last unexplored frontier in the Land of Dawn. All the way down from surface, the sun fades away and the temperature drops, then there is complete darkness. It is called the Abysmal Sea, where currents and the high pressure are strong enough to tear apart any advanced materials Eruditio has invented. This place is a forbidden zone of life, where no human has ever set foot in. Only the remains of those abandoned and eliminated civilizations have been sinking and piling up.Nevertheless, it is not only death here. Many unbelievable and indescribable creatures, including Atlas, have been struggling and multiplying for ages in this dangerous area. They were among the oldest living things on the Land of Dawn, devouring elemental creatures for power, which made them imprisoned in this deepest place by the Ancient Ones. The powerful Injunction blocked light, heat as well as their upward path. In order to adapt to the high-pressure environment, they removed their shells and redundant structures, and developed a variety of fluid shapes. In the endless darkness, there is no fight and strife, only the law of survival: existence, alternation and circulation.&lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>