<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Profile on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/tags/profile.html</link><description>Recent content in Profile on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:04:16 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/profile/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Profile Dreams</title><link>/profile/dreams.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:04:16 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/dreams.html</guid><description> Dreams &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Dreams Bio #1 Dreams SocMed Dreams Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Dreams Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Taka</title><link>/profile/taka.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:04:06 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/taka.html</guid><description> Taka &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Taka Bio #1 Taka SocMed Taka Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Taka Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Branz</title><link>/profile/branz.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:03:56 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/branz.html</guid><description> Branz &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Branz Bio #1 Branz SocMed Branz Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Branz Latest Build # BRANZ Info</description></item><item><title>Profile Rippo</title><link>/profile/rippo.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:03:38 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/rippo.html</guid><description> Rippo &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Rippo Bio #1 Rippo SocMed Rippo Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Rippo Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Bravo</title><link>/profile/bravo.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:03:29 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/bravo.html</guid><description> Bravo &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Bravo Bio #1 Bravo SocMed Bravo Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Bravo Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Kyy</title><link>/profile/kyy.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:03:20 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/kyy.html</guid><description> Kyy &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Kyy Bio #1 Kyy SocMed Kyy Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Kyy Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Clayyy</title><link>/profile/clayyy.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 18:39:55 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/clayyy.html</guid><description> Clayyy &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Clayyy Bio #1 Clayyy SocMed Instagram Clayyy Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Clayyy Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Psychoo</title><link>/profile/psychoo.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 18:38:49 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/psychoo.html</guid><description> Psychoo &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Psychoo Bio #1 Psychoo SocMed Instagram Psychoo Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Psychoo Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Skylar</title><link>/profile/skylar.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 18:37:08 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/skylar.html</guid><description> Skylar &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Skylar Bio #1 Skylar SocMed Instagram Skylar Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Skylar Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Wizzking</title><link>/profile/wizzking.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 18:34:58 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/wizzking.html</guid><description> Wizzking &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Wizzking Bio #1 Wizzking SocMed Youtube Instagram Wizzking Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Wizzking Latest Build # WIZZKING Info</description></item><item><title>Profile Liam</title><link>/profile/liam.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 18:33:52 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/liam.html</guid><description> Liam &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Liam Bio #1 Liam SocMed Instagram Liam Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Liam Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile R7</title><link>/profile/r7.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 18:32:28 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/r7.html</guid><description> R7 &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info R7 Bio #1 R7 SocMed Youtube Instagram R7 Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO R7 Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Vyn</title><link>/profile/vyn.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 18:16:56 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/vyn.html</guid><description> Vyn &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Vyn Bio #1 Vyn SocMed Youtube Instagram Vyn Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Vyn Latest Build #</description></item><item><title>Profile Alberttt</title><link>/profile/alberttt.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 02:28:06 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/alberttt.html</guid><description>ALBERTTT Team RRQ Alberttt &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports ALBERTTT sports_esports Team RRQ Close More Info Alberttt Bio Introduction Sejak kecil, Albert Nielsen Iskandar memang hobi bermain gim. Ketika gim Mobile Legends rilis, pemuda kelahiran Bali ini pun langsung menyukainya, terus memainkannya, dan tertarik untuk terjun ke ranah kompetitif.Perjalanan kariernya sebagai pro player Mobile Legends dimulai dari tim biasa, sering disebut tim tongkrongan, yang berada di kampung halamannya tersebut.</description></item><item><title>Profile Xinnn</title><link>/profile/xinnn.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 04:53:57 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/xinnn.html</guid><description> xinnn Team RRQ Xinnn &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports xinnn sports_esports Team RRQ Close More Info Xinnn Bio #1 Xinnn SocMed Xinnn SocMed Youtube Instagram Xinnn Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Xinnn Latest Build # XINNN Info XINN Info</description></item><item><title>Profile Violet</title><link>/profile/violet.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 01:41:07 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/violet.html</guid><description> Evos Esports Evos Violet &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Evos Esports Close More Info Evos Violet Bio #1 Evos Violet SocMed Youtube Instagram Evos Violet Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Evos Violet Latest Build # VIOLET Info</description></item><item><title>Profile Evos Pica</title><link>/profile/pica.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 01:14:33 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/pica.html</guid><description>pica Evos Lynx Pica &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports pica sports_esports Evos Lynx Jessica Pica adalah salah satu pro player game Mobile Legends. Pica panggilan akrabnya , mulai dikenal ketika dirinya bergabung bersama salah satu tim esports ternama Indonesia yaitu EVOS Esports. Yap , bergabung Pica bersama EVOS menandakan dirinya tidak hanya modal tampang doang , tapi Pica juga hebat dan galak ketika berada di arena Land Of Dawn.</description></item><item><title>Profile Spade</title><link>/profile/spade.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 19:41:30 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/spade.html</guid><description> Onic Esports Spade &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Onic Esports Close More Info Spade Bio #1 Spade SocMed Spade Latest Build # SPADE Info</description></item><item><title>Profile Celiboy</title><link>/profile/celiboy.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:39:16 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/celiboy.html</guid><description>Celiboy Alter Egos Esports Celiboy &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports Celiboy sports_esports Alter Egos Esports Close More Info Celiboy Bio Biodata #1 Celiboy adalah pemain muda yang telah memperkuat Alter Ego sejak MPL S4. Pemain yang terkenal dengan the miracle boy ini berhasil menorehkan rekor kill terbanyak di musim debutnya di MPL S4.Sebelum memperkuat Alter Ego, Celiboy sempat bergabung bersama Team Capcorn (TCN) yang akhirnya diakuisisi oleh Rex Regum Qeon (RRQ).</description></item><item><title>Profile AE Ahmad</title><link>/profile/ahmad.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:16:31 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/ahmad.html</guid><description>ahmad Alter Ego Esports AE Ahmad &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports ahmad sports_esports Alter Ego Esports Close More Info AE Ahmad Bio Biodata #1 Maungzy adalah pemain professional MLBB dari Pontianak. Pemain ini terkenal dari permainan Gusionnya yang sangat cepat dan membunuh. Pada MPL S3 atau turnamen perdananya, Maungzy dipercaya mengomandoi Alter Ego dari posisi Midlane.Kedatangan Eldhin Rahadian Putra AKA Celiboy membuat Maungzy mengganti posisinya menjadi Hardcarry di lane bawah.</description></item><item><title>Profile Zxuan</title><link>/profile/zxuan.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 13:07:15 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/zxuan.html</guid><description> zhenxml Evos SG Zxuan &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports zhenxml sports_esports Evos SG Close More Info Zxuan Bio #1 Zxuan SocMed Youtube Facebook Instagram Zxuan Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Zxuan Latest Build # ZXUAN Info</description></item><item><title>Profile Antimage</title><link>/profile/antimage.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 02:02:18 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/antimage.html</guid><description>Antimage Evos Esports MPL ID S7 Antimage &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports Antimage sports_esports Evos Esports Close More Info Antimage Bio Intermezo #1 Sangat dikenal dengan gaya permainan yang bar-bar, Antimage memang tak pandang bulu saat bertarung di Land of Dawn. Bercita-cita ingin menjadi pengacara, nyatanya ia saat ini tak melanjutkan kuliahnya. Meski menjadi punggawa Onic Esports sejak MPL ID Season 2, nyatanya ia baru bisa menunjukkan kualitas terbaiknya di Season 3.</description></item><item><title>Profile Oura</title><link>/profile/oura.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 15:04:15 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/oura.html</guid><description>Biawak Batam Genk Kapak M1 Oura &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports Biawak Batam sports_esports Genk Kapak Close More Info Oura Bio Biografi Evos Oura #1 Di kalangan para gaming nama evos oura sudah tidak asing lagi didengar Doi adalah kapten dari tim Evos eSports divisi Mobile Legends. Yang sangat hebat dalam memainkan game nya di dunia online.Cowok yang punya nama lengkap Eko Julianto ini sudah menggeluti dunia game semenjak dahulu dan selalu bermain game secara baik.</description></item><item><title>Markocop</title><link>/profile/markocop.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 04:42:12 +0700</pubDate><guid>/profile/markocop.html</guid><description> Markocop &amp;times; Youtube facebook Facebook photo_camera Instagram flutter_dash Twitter sports_esports sports_esports Close More Info Markocop SocMed Youtube Markocop Latest Video Loading Video... PLAY VIDEO Markocop Latest Build # MARKOCOP Info</description></item><item><title/><link>/hero/diggie.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/diggie.html</guid><description>&amp;times; HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Scholars and thinkers from all over the world gather at the city of Antoinerei. It is here where the commonly overlooked Digger lives. Many don&amp;#39;t give a second look to Digger due to his small frame, until they come upon his researches in chronoscience. Digger loves clocks, he believes that within these little mechanical toys lies many more yet to be discovered secrets. Through the use of his &amp;#34;Time Nest&amp;#34; Digger can control the flow of time.</description></item><item><title>akai</title><link>/hero/akai.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/akai.html</guid><description>&amp;times; AKAI HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; A clumsy panda from a far away Eastern villages dreams every night of becoming a mighty warrior. Akai is fat and clumsy even for panda standards and most people say that all he&amp;#39;s good for is rolling round. However, this never fazed Akai, as he trained daily, hoping to one day achieve his dreams of becoming a respected warrior. His friends mocked him, his parents discouraged him but Akai persisted.</description></item><item><title>aldous</title><link>/hero/aldous.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/aldous.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ALDOUS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Legends from the Land of Dawn say that the Western Desert&amp;#39;s Minoan Kingdom possesses a mysterious labyrinth. In the maze is a statue of a giant minotaur, which the people consider to be the mecca of the Minoan Kingdom. Some say that there is a group of mercenaries who guard the entire maze. ??The Kingdom produced a lot of precious jade, which brought the Minoan people great wealth.</description></item><item><title>alice</title><link>/hero/alice.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/alice.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ALICE HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Thousands of years ago, the humans defeated the Blood Demons and imprisoned their queen Alice in the dark abyss. Today, the land of dawn faces a huge disturbance and the seal&amp;#39;s power has slowly weakened. The dominator of dark abyss is thirsty for more believers and dark force has been growing stronger in secret. With the acquiescence of the great dominator, Alice broke free from her ancient prison.</description></item><item><title>alpha</title><link>/hero/alpha.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/alpha.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ALPHA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Alpha is another creation of Laboratory 1718 after Saber left. Mad scientists got a new idea from a famous sci-fi movie. Using human bodies as biological material and space meteorolite as metal skeletons, they created powerful twins. Alpha and Beta, also known as &amp;#39;Flesh Weapon&amp;#39;, are capable of utilizing a supernatural power that&amp;#39;s ubiquitous but very mystery. However, the twins had always had a strong conscience, and refused to become killing machines.</description></item><item><title>alucard</title><link>/hero/alucard.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/alucard.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ALUCARD HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; When just a child, both of Alucard&amp;#39;s parents were killed by demons and he was imprisoned and suffered cruelties at their hands for several months, until finally he was rescued by demon hunters and raised by them. From a young age, he was raised to be an outstanding demon hunter, with an extreme enmity for the demon race. The three iron laws of the demon hunters are: Swear no allegiance to any army.</description></item><item><title>angela</title><link>/hero/angela.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/angela.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ANGELA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Dr. Baker was one of the founders of Lab 1718, an institution created with the aim of bringing peace to the world. But as his co-founders fell deeper and deeper into their depraved human weaponization experiments, Dr. Baker felt he had no choice but to leave and pursue a new project. Renouncing the questionable ethics of human experimentation, he endeavored to create a new kind of lifeform, solely from a mechanical skeleton, puppet strings, and synthetic skin, and finally, a new generation of artificial life was born.</description></item><item><title>argus</title><link>/hero/argus.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/argus.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ARGUS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Argus and Rafaela were heavenly angels that descended into the land of dawn at the same time. One responsible for eradicating evil, the other for eradicating suffering. As Argus went through countless battles, he soon became obsessed with the pursuit of power. One time during a battle he heard the call of an ancient being, Argus soon lost control of his ambitions and became corrupted.</description></item><item><title>atlas</title><link>/hero/atlas.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/atlas.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ATLAS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The dark, cold and mysterious deep sea is the last unexplored frontier in the Land of Dawn. All the way down from surface, the sun fades away and the temperature drops, then there is complete darkness. It is called the Abysmal Sea, where currents and the high pressure are strong enough to tear apart any advanced materials Eruditio has invented. This place is a forbidden zone of life, where no human has ever set foot in.</description></item><item><title>aurora</title><link>/hero/aurora.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/aurora.html</guid><description>&amp;times; AURORA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Aurora, born in a windstorm and with a great power of controlling ice and snow, is the queen of the northernmost land - Nost Gal, the dominator of the Frozen Sea and the Guardian of the Land of Dawn. Although they are all on this northernmost land, Aurora never had any interest in the conflicts between Franco and Bane. She was born powerful and extraordinary.</description></item><item><title>badang</title><link>/hero/badang.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/badang.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BADANG HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Long ago there was a small village resting in the southern regions of the Land of Dawn. The villagers were very hardworking, fishing day and night for a living. Among them was a strong man, named Badang. Enthusiastic and brave, he tirelessly helped everyone solve their difficulties in life. However, a strange thing happened in the village not long ago. The villagers got up early every day to catch fish.</description></item><item><title>balmond</title><link>/hero/balmond.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/balmond.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BALMOND HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The renowned Bloodaxe Orcs are the descendants of interbreeding between blood demons and other devils, and their custom of using arcane magic to infect the entire bodies of their enemies and animals with blood is a testament to this fact. They are bloodthirsty and war-loving, and the strongest among them is named Balmond BALMOND MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Fighter Lane: EXP Lane Tier : A Tier BP : 6500 DM : 299 Ticket : 0 balmond &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Balmond Skills 1 &amp;times; Bloodthirst</description></item><item><title>bane</title><link>/hero/bane.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/bane.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BANE HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Many years ago, Captain Bane roamed the seas on his ship, the Black Pearl, and the ever-victorious sea dwellers called him Lord of the Seven Seas. Today he has awakened from the briny depths, bringing his cursed body and a tattered Black Pearl back to these waters. He must announce his return to the sea dwellers and renew his reign here. BANE MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Fighter Lane: ROAM Tier : A Tier BP : 6500 DM : 254 Ticket : 0 bane &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Bane Skills 1 &amp;times; Shark Bite</description></item><item><title>barats</title><link>/hero/barats.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/barats.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BARATS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; BARATS MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Tank Lane: EXP Lane Tier : A Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : barats &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Barats Skills 1 &amp;times; Big Guy
Each time Barats and Detona deal damage to a target with their skills, Detona gains 1 stack of (Big Guy) for 12s, capped at 25 stacks. For each stack of (Big Guy), Detona gains increased body size, 2-5 Physical &amp;amp; Magic Defense, and 2% Resilience.</description></item><item><title>baxia</title><link>/hero/baxia.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/baxia.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BAXIA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In the east of the Land of Dawn, between the old village Stream Valley and the Scarlet Shadow, a huge totem ruin stands among the mountains and forests. Some believe that it symbolizes a kind of faith or, as an oracle claimed, is guarding the land. Not far from it, there are mysterious stone steps covered by some leaves. The winding stone steps reach to the sky.</description></item><item><title>beatrix</title><link>/hero/beatrix.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/beatrix.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BEATRIX HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; BEATRIX MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Marksman Lane: Gold Lane Tier : A&amp;#43; Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 beatrix &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Beatrix Skills 1 &amp;times; Renner
Close Beatrix Skills 2 &amp;times; Mechanical Genius
Her extraordinary talent in the field of mechanics allowed Beatrix to produce 4 weapon(s) of truly awe-inspiring firepower. @{E1058003|1|10510|(Renner) Basic Attack - Longshot: Fire a powerful shot in the enemy's current direction, dealing 125( +500% Total Physical ATK) (Physical Damage) to the first target hit (this shot can be dodged, or blocked by others.</description></item><item><title>belerick</title><link>/hero/belerick.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/belerick.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BELERICK HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Legends say, the Ancient Ones of the Land of Dawn trusted mystical creatures with grand tasks. ########Belerick, a member of the tree people, was one of this creatures. Belerick’s heart is filled with nothing but kindness—He absolutely hates conflict. Within his ancient self, Belerick possesses a strong life force that provides strong resistance against a attacks, but also allows him to reincarnate. Due to his kind nature, wherever there is conflcit, Belerick will be there to help the righteous and weak.</description></item><item><title>benedetta</title><link>/hero/benedetta.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/benedetta.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BENEDETTA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; BENEDETTA MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Assassins Lane: EXP Lane Tier : S&amp;#43; Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 benedetta &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Benedetta Skills 1 &amp;times; Phantom Slash
Benedetta withdraws swiftly and leaves a shadow in front. After a short delay, her shadow slashes forward in a fan-shaped area, dealing 200( +60% Total Physical ATK) (Physical Damage) and slowing the enemies by 60% for 0.</description></item><item><title>brody</title><link>/hero/brody.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/brody.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BRODY HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; BRODY MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Marksman Lane: Gold Lane Tier : S&amp;#43; Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : brody &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Brody Skills 1 &amp;times; Abyss Corrosion
With his Basic Attacks resonated with the Abyss Power within his body, Brody is able to move while winding up his Basic Attacks (which will be interrupted when casting skills), at the cost of having longer Basic Attack Animation and lower Attack Speed Bonus.</description></item><item><title>bruno</title><link>/hero/bruno.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/bruno.html</guid><description>&amp;times; BRUNO HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Born in the slums, Bruno was always more frail than other children his age, but this did not prevent him from having a heart that yearned for freedom. One day in a terrible incident, Bruno lost both of his legs trying to save a friend, causing him to pretty much give up on life. The scholars of Eruditio however heard his story, and out of pity for his misfortune and admiration for his bravery, they decided to use the city&amp;#39;s most advanced technology to make a new pair of legs for him.</description></item><item><title>carmilla</title><link>/hero/carmilla.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/carmilla.html</guid><description>&amp;times; CARMILLA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Many years ago, Carmilla was born in the House Ansaac in the Castle Aberleen. As the only daughter of the Earl, she was loved by all her family since birth. When she grew up, her eminent family background coupled with her captivating beauty made her one of the most popular noble ladies around the Castle Aberleen, and maybe even the whole Empire. However, her royal origin was inevitably bound to the tragedy as was to become a political tool of her father Earl Anssac, CARMILLA MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Supports Lane: ROAM Tier : A Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 carmilla &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Carmilla Skills 1 &amp;times; Vampire Pact</description></item><item><title>cecilion</title><link>/hero/cecilion.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/cecilion.html</guid><description>&amp;times; CECILION HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Many years ago, enjoying the night opera performed by Cecilion was the most popular form of entertainment for the people of Castle Aberleen. It was always full house at the theatre each time this most famous opera actor performed. Everyone was attracted by his indescribable beauty and talent. However, the applause, love and cheers from human beings didn’t make Cecilion feel happy. He was one of the Blood Demons, and it was hard for him to open his mind to humans.</description></item><item><title>change</title><link>/hero/change.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/change.html</guid><description>&amp;times; CHANGE HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Chang’e is the youngest disciple of the Great Dragon. From an early age, she exhibited amazing magical potential, quickly mastering the Great Dragon’s greatest spell — The Sacred Satellite. From then on, Chang’e earned the Great Dragons eternal love. However, Chang’e had a energetic and fun-loving personality that gave the Great Dragon quite a few headaches. Finally, he asked Zilong, his adopted son, to look after Chang’e.</description></item><item><title>chou</title><link>/hero/chou.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/chou.html</guid><description>&amp;times; CHOU HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Chou was born in a secluded slum deep in the hearts of poverty, living the lowest quality of life. Despite the dreadful conditions Chou still kept his heart of kindness, as day in day out he continued to look after the old and the young there with passion. At that time, there was great turmoil and unrest in the Land of the Dawn; mayhem spread throughout the land and eventually started to affect this small remote area.</description></item><item><title>claude</title><link>/hero/claude.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/claude.html</guid><description>&amp;times; CLAUDE HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; If you often go to the tavern, then you must have heard of Claude. His story is a favorite for tipsy travelers—One of the most famous legends in the Land of Dawn. Rumor has it, that this teenage human has a special talent for thievery. To Claude, thievery is an art from rather than a crime. In fact, Claude would often send his victims a notice to let them know in advance.</description></item><item><title>clint</title><link>/hero/clint.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/clint.html</guid><description>&amp;times; CLINT HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; No one knows where he comes from or why he fights, but everyone born in the Wastelands knows that he is the only semblance of justice in these parts. Even the boldest of thieves wouldn&amp;#39;t dare to challenge Clint and his six shooters. With his lightning reflexes and unparalleled accuracy, a flurry of bullets would be buried in his enemies&amp;#39; foreheads before they had time to blink.</description></item><item><title>cyclops</title><link>/hero/cyclops.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/cyclops.html</guid><description>&amp;times; CYCLOPS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Cyclops is a giant with only one eye, yes, at least he is in his own homeland. Cyclops were obsessed with stars and skies when he was little. He watched all days and nights and discovered the truth that planets were moving all the time. And this kind of movements, it contains unbelievable magic power. With an hourglass to load and control this kind of power, he became the famous &amp;#39;Starsoul Magician&amp;#39; in his homeland.</description></item><item><title>dyrroth</title><link>/hero/dyrroth.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/dyrroth.html</guid><description>&amp;times; DYRROTH HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Thirty years ago, a prince was born in the Moniyan Empire. He was a symbol of salvation and justice for his people. It was believed that he would lead the Moniyan Empire in unifying the Land of Dawn. The Empire Nobles gave everything to the prince. On the day of prince’s first birthday he was found dead in his baby bed blanketed in blood.</description></item><item><title>esmeralda</title><link>/hero/esmeralda.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/esmeralda.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ESMERALDA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The astrologers, who have constantly been observing astrospace, possess the occult abilities to explain and predict everything in the world, including both about their processes and results. To become an astrologer, candidates should pass rigorous assessments, which will test both their willpower and astrological abilities. Going down the generations, the elders finally select Esmeralda, a young girl living in the Western Desert, to be the new successor in the Land of Dawn.</description></item><item><title>estes</title><link>/hero/estes.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/estes.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ESTES HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; At the habitat of moon elves, somewhere west of the Moonlake, here locates the legendary Emerald Woodland, which was the birthplace of the first generation of elves. Every elven king was born in the Tree of Life at the center of the Emerald Woodland. The elven king of present generation is the unique Estes, who was badly hurt during the second plane war and had to go into sleep in the Emerald Woodland.</description></item><item><title>eudora</title><link>/hero/eudora.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/eudora.html</guid><description>&amp;times; EUDORA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Ever since she was an apprentice wizard, Eudora&amp;#39;s special talent for controlling lightning always shocked (no pun intended) her many teachers. After a brief period of study, her teachers discovered she had already mastered all they had to teach her. Yearning to continue her progress, Eudora set foot on the road to the Land of Dawn, believing that her lightning magic could reach new heights in that turbulent land.</description></item><item><title>fanny</title><link>/hero/fanny.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/fanny.html</guid><description>&amp;times; FANNY HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Despite just being a human, Fanny never gave up on her dream of flying. She fashioned a kind of steel grappling hook for herself in the hopes of using it to grab onto cliff faces and soar between mountain peaks. After countless training sessions in live environments, Fanny has finally mastered this technique. Folks who have seen her soaring through the air refer to her as the Blade of Freedom.</description></item><item><title>faramis</title><link>/hero/faramis.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/faramis.html</guid><description>&amp;times; FARAMIS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Far from the Moniyan Empire stands an ancient castle. This castle has a glorious history comparable to the Moniyan Empire. Unfortunately, the castle collapsed overnight, as if it had suddenly disappeared. The tall gray walls were covered with dark black vines, which were more horrifying and strange under the moonlight. The breath of death makes the creatures close to this ancient building shudder and keep away.</description></item><item><title>franco</title><link>/hero/franco.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/franco.html</guid><description>&amp;times; FRANCO HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Franco&amp;#39;s home is in the eternally frozen seas beyond the land of Nost Gal. This continent of ice and snow is where the sea people have made a life for themselves, but the resurrection of Captain Bane has destroyed their formerly peaceful lives. Franco and his comrades have banded together to oppose Bane&amp;#39;s rule and bring peace back to the sea FRANCO MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Tank Lane: ROAM Tier : A Tier BP : 32000 DM : 0 Ticket : 749 franco &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Franco Skills 1 &amp;times; Wasteland Force</description></item><item><title>freya</title><link>/hero/freya.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/freya.html</guid><description>&amp;times; FREYA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In the far northern reaches of Nost Gal, there is a legend: When a warrior dies on the battlefield, the goddess of war Freya will come down from heaven, kiss the spirit of the fallen, and lead it to the Temple of Heroes, where former warriors can have a new life. Freya herself is an outstanding warrior. She can both attack and defend with her sword and shield, and at a critical moment in battle she can transform into a halberd and smash the enemy formation.</description></item><item><title>gatotkaca</title><link>/hero/gatotkaca.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/gatotkaca.html</guid><description>&amp;times; GATOTKACA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Gatotkaca &amp;#39;The Iron Bone&amp;#39; was the son of Bima and Arimbi from Arcapada universe.Since his childhood, he&amp;#39;s been a champion of Gods, fights vicious enemies of his homeland. Once lost and beaten near death,Gatotkaca arise as a mighty warrior from Pandava clan who possessed the supernatural power he got from the ultimate training inside the cauldron of heaven, Candradimuka.With his Antakusuma armor and Brajamusti-Brajadenta twin gauntlet, he can fly across the skies like lightning and hunt down his enemies, the furious Ashuras.</description></item><item><title>gloo</title><link>/hero/gloo.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/gloo.html</guid><description>&amp;times; GLOO HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; GLOO MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Tank Lane: ROAM Tier : A&amp;#43; Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 gloo &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Gloo Skills 1 &amp;times; Slam, Slam
Gloo reaches out and slams the ground, dealing 360(+80% Total Magic Power) (Magic Damage) to the enemy. On the final location, a (Goo) is left behind, and after 3s it explodes to deal 270(+60% Total Magic Power) (Magic Damage) to nearby enemies, immobilizing them for 1s.</description></item><item><title>gord</title><link>/hero/gord.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/gord.html</guid><description>&amp;times; GORD HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Gord was born in a magic world, and from birth manipulating magic energy was like breathing air to him. His love of mystic magic was particularly powerful, and almost immediately he was able to master some of the most profound mystic spells in all of magic. As he slowly grew older, his reliance on mystic energy became more severe, until finally mystic emblems seeped into his skin and bones and transformed his appearance.</description></item><item><title>granger</title><link>/hero/granger.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/granger.html</guid><description>&amp;times; GRANGER HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; There was once a tale going around the Land of Dawn about a musician. No one knew where he came from nor where he was headed. Everyone just called him “the vagrant poet, Granger”. Granger was orphaned during the war between the Moniyan Empire and the Southern Mountains. He was picked up by the Imperial Army, then sent to the Monastery of Light. Similar to all orphans, Granger was silent and isolated.</description></item><item><title>grock</title><link>/hero/grock.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/grock.html</guid><description>&amp;times; GROCK HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Deep within the mountains of the Land of Dawn sits an ancient fortress. Though the owner is unknown, it is rumored that it could be a descendant of the legendary race that once walked the Lands of Dawn. It said that this race is older than the earth itself, having a special affinity for nature, they were able to build deep connections and relations with various beings of nature, especially the Stone Titans.</description></item><item><title>guinevere</title><link>/hero/guinevere.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/guinevere.html</guid><description>&amp;times; GUINEVERE HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The Baroque family is one of the few nobles on the Land of Dawn. The most prestigious skill of them, fencing, the family&amp;#39;s emblem, discourages countless opponents from even thinking about attacking. In addition, beauty and wisdom are also the most perfect genetic signs of the Baroque family, just like the eternal beauty and love of Violet. GUINEVERE MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Fighter Lane: EXP Lane Tier : S Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 guinevere &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Guinevere Skills 1 &amp;times; Super Magic</description></item><item><title>gusion</title><link>/hero/gusion.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/gusion.html</guid><description>&amp;times; GUSION HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The Paxley family is one of the most powerful and prestigious magic families in the Land of Dawn, and each member is raised to become a mage of the finest order. In their eyes, the path of the magician is the most sacred and noble vocation there is, and all those who brandish a sword in battle are merely weak, dim-witted fools. Gusion, however, is determined to break the mold.</description></item><item><title>hanabi</title><link>/hero/hanabi.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/hanabi.html</guid><description>&amp;times; HANABI HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Hanabi received the teachings of the Scarlet Shadow ninja sect&amp;#39;s Supreme Grandmaster from a young age, exhibiting natural talent that far exceeded any of her peers, until she met a young shadow ninja called Hayabusa. This was the very first time the proud Hanabi came across anyone who could hold their own against her. Whenever the moon was full, Hanabi would try to find ways to provoke this young shadow ninja into dueling with her, however, she could never defeat this youngster, who fused spiritualism with shadow techniques to create a unique and powerful style.</description></item><item><title>hanzo</title><link>/hero/hanzo.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/hanzo.html</guid><description>&amp;times; HANZO HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Long ago, the House of Akakage was hailed as the Gods of Ninja Arts. For generations, the Akakages researched and taught advanced ninjutsu. In order to achieve the pinnacle of ninja arts, the Akakages used a forbidden ninjutsu to rid their hearts of evil, anger, and greed by condensing them into a demon called, Hanekage. No one expected that Hanekage would have consciousness, despite lurking within their bodies.</description></item><item><title>harith</title><link>/hero/harith.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/harith.html</guid><description>&amp;times; HARITH HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In the Magic Forest lives the race of gremlins. They&amp;#39;re small, naughty creatures with high intelligence and independent traits. They have been the most faithful ally to the Moon Elf since the history begins. Harith was born with outstanding mind, he soon became the best wizard among the Feline Race. The Feline People are a peaceful kind that seeks tranquility. They have never stepped out of the Magic Forest once.</description></item><item><title>harley</title><link>/hero/harley.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/harley.html</guid><description>&amp;times; HARLEY HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; There lived a famous young mage - Harley in the Lion Academy of Magical City. He is blessed by the Magical Goddess and as the star of the Academy, he is able to learn quickly and master any magical spell. Kids need adventure when Harley and his friends were exploring the jungle in the middle of the night, they overheard the evil conspiracy of the organization called &amp;#34;Dark Wizards&amp;#34;.</description></item><item><title>hayabusa</title><link>/hero/hayabusa.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/hayabusa.html</guid><description>&amp;times; HAYABUSA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In the town of Iga, the strongest ninja of every generation receives the title of Shadow, responsible for the most dangerous and difficult missions, protecting the town of Iga day in and day out, all without the knowledge of its inhabitants. At present, the freshly-anointed Shadow of Iga, Hayabusa, has been transported to the Land of Dawn to carry out the most dangerous and difficult of missions: find and kill the previous generation&amp;#39;s Shadow who betrayed and killed his friend, the one who was once lauded as the greatest ninja Iga had seen in centuries.</description></item><item><title>helcurt</title><link>/hero/helcurt.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/helcurt.html</guid><description>&amp;times; HELCURT HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In the museum records of the Lord of Dawn, there is said to be a mysterious race that once forged a great empire. This race was blessed with the power to swallow up light, for they are able to temporarily blackout a space. This was not the only talent they possessed, as they also had the ability to blink through physical space, being able to surprise enemies for a sneak attack.</description></item><item><title>hilda</title><link>/hero/hilda.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/hilda.html</guid><description>&amp;times; HILDA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; On the Megalith Wasteland, there are only giant rocks and some sparse bushes in sight. It&amp;#39;s a very infertile land where Hilda and her people lived. The infertility of the land required everyone in the clan to become a good hunter in order to acquire precious meat. Born with great strength, Hilda soon became the leader of the hunting party and led her people to harvest abundant food.</description></item><item><title>hylos</title><link>/hero/hylos.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/hylos.html</guid><description>&amp;times; HYLOS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Amidst the misty mountains within the northern reaches of the Land of Dawn, reside an ancient and mysterious race of Centaurs. These centaurs guard a fountain that rests on the highest mountain peak. This fountain is said to give the gift of life. Dark forces have relentlessly tried to gain the power found within the waters of this fountain, but only to be time and time again be thwarted by the centaurs.</description></item><item><title>irithel</title><link>/hero/irithel.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/irithel.html</guid><description>&amp;times; IRITHEL HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Irithel was abandoned in the jungle by her parents when she was a little girl. Under the guidance of the God of Jungle, a female smilodon that had just given birth adopted her. Being protected by the mother smilodon, the little smilodon Leo and Irithel learned to hunt, survive and grew up like an animal. During a territory fight, the mother smilodon was badly injured.</description></item><item><title>jawhead</title><link>/hero/jawhead.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/jawhead.html</guid><description>&amp;times; JAWHEAD HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Clandestine organizations have existed throughout the many ages of the Land of Dawn&amp;#39;s history. No one knows the true purpose of these organizations, but one thing is for sure, whenever a crisis is at hand, mysterious figures emerge from the shadows to restore order to the world.Professor Henry and his wife worked for the Dawn Council, known for its research in cutting-edge technology, providing an endless and varied stream of high-tech products to government agencies and mysterious, anonymous clients.</description></item><item><title>johnson</title><link>/hero/johnson.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/johnson.html</guid><description>&amp;times; JOHNSON HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Johnson, with a hardy constitution as a rock, when he ran through the dome stadium like a heavy truck, the cheers of girls Burst out loud. He led the team to lift the champion&amp;#39;s trophies and achieved his peak of his life as a super quarterback with millions fans around. However, fortune is always fickle. A little girl rushed to the road in a sudden while Johnson was driving his sport car.</description></item><item><title>kadita</title><link>/hero/kadita.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/kadita.html</guid><description>&amp;times; KADITA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The Queen of the Southern Seas, Kadita, was once the princess of a small island nation. Admired by everyone, Kadita was considered by all to be genuine, intelligent, and kind hearted. Though, fate often times finds its way to hit people with strife. Kadita was no different. As the heir apparent to the king, a member within the royal family grew jealous of Kadita and conspired to ruin her — An unknown mage wielding the power of black magic viciously attacked the princess.</description></item><item><title>kagura</title><link>/hero/kagura.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/kagura.html</guid><description>&amp;times; KAGURA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Onmyouji Master is a master of the yin yang arts, driven by powerful spirits, yin and yang. The Kagura family is the oldest and most powerful of the Onmyouji, with the most powerful of all being the Ancestor Master. Kagura, as one in the Onmyouji family with the most potentials, had been given the Seimei umbrella, an heirloom of yin yang arts passed down through generations.</description></item><item><title>kaja</title><link>/hero/kaja.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/kaja.html</guid><description>&amp;times; KAJA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The Celestial Palace, home of the gods, was once a bustling city patrolled by innumerable Nazar guardians. Any demon who dared approach the city would be overwhelmed by their peerless flying speed and bound by their fearsome lightning whips which would strip their victims of all magical abilities. No demon could escape when pursued by these divine warriors, and thus perpetual peace was maintained in the Celestial Palace.</description></item><item><title>karina</title><link>/hero/karina.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/karina.html</guid><description>&amp;times; KARINA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Unlike the friendly moon elves, night elves were born into a world of darkness which casts a gloom on and twists their personalities. They offer their services as assassins to the other races, as all night elves are born killers. Karina is a standout amongst them. KARINA MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Assassins Lane: Jungle Tier : A Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 karina &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Karina Skills 1 &amp;times; Shadow Combo</description></item><item><title>karrie</title><link>/hero/karrie.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/karrie.html</guid><description>&amp;times; KARRIE HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Alaghat is a mysterious technique empire. There lives a strange humanoid race - Yasson. They are in human shape while having a pair of deformed feet. They are agile and born to fight. Meanwhile, they are also good at techniques that allow them to create a significant civilization and to invade the others. Since Karrie was a child, she was very talented and trained into an excellent and arrogant warrior leader, but at the same time, she lost her feelings and became a machine.</description></item><item><title>khaleed</title><link>/hero/khaleed.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/khaleed.html</guid><description>&amp;times; KHALEED HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; KHALEED MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Fighter Lane: EXP Lane Tier : B Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : khaleed &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Khaleed Skills 1 &amp;times; Sand Walk
Khaleed accumulates (Desert Power) while moving. After (Desert Power) is fully charged, Khaleed will slide on sand, increasing Movement Speed by 25% and enhancing his next Basic Attack. With the enhanced Basic Attack, Khaleed dashes to the target and raises a wave of surging sand, dealing ( +160% Total Physical ATK) (Physical Damage) to the target and enemies behind and leaving a pool of sand for 2s.</description></item><item><title>khufra</title><link>/hero/khufra.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/khufra.html</guid><description>&amp;times; KHUFRA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In the far reaches of the Western Desert, an ancient city lays hidden among the sands. Despite ages passing by, the desert sands were unable to devour this city, which stands proud and majestic in a sea of emptiness. Scholars of antiquities have long spoke of this fabled city, whose most infamous ruler was none other than Khufra. KHUFRA MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Tank Lane: ROAM Tier : S Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 khufra &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Khufra Skills 1 &amp;times; Spell Curse</description></item><item><title>kimmy</title><link>/hero/kimmy.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/kimmy.html</guid><description>&amp;times; KIMMY HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Kimmy grew up in a military family. She was encouraged by her father, a renowned general of the Moniyan Empire, to be straightforward, self-disciplined and obedient. As a result, Kimmy developed a tomboy-ish character which everyone could see, be it in the way she dressed or in the way she spoke. Since childhood, Kimmy possessed a natural talent for research and innovation. Kimmy was always keen on analyzing and reforming chemical energies.</description></item><item><title>lancelot</title><link>/hero/lancelot.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/lancelot.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LANCELOT HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Lancelot hails from the Baroque family in the Land of Dawn, where at a young age he showed exquisite talent in the art of fencing, garnering the praise of the masses, so much so that he became lost in the admiration. When the magical tribes of the attacked, Lancelot, who had just awoken from a drunken stupor, arrogantly attacked them alone. After winning a few battles, he dropped his guard and pursued the remaining forces in arrogance but soon the magical tribes regrouped and defeated him within the mountains.</description></item><item><title>lapulapu</title><link>/hero/lapulapu.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/lapulapu.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LAPULAPU HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The mysterious waters to the south of the Land of Dawn are dotted with islands big and small. Here the land is fertile, the climate mild. Life thrives, and food is in abundance. People live lives of peace and happiness. But one day, a group of invaders came upon this peaceful land and disrupted the happy lives of the people. The chief of Makadan Island, Lapu-Lapu, refused to become anyone&amp;#39;s slave.</description></item><item><title>layla</title><link>/hero/layla.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/layla.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LAYLA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The world Layla lives in is full of a force called Malefic Energy, a savage and unruly energy that causes all living things that come in contact with it to lose their reason and become rabidly ferocious. This energy had all but wiped out her world, until one day Layla&amp;#39;s father discovered a way to use a gun forged from magic iron from deep within the earth to absorb and control Malefic Energy.</description></item><item><title>leomord</title><link>/hero/leomord.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/leomord.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LEOMORD HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; On a day much like today, Tigreal and his Expeditionary Forces of Light charged into the Fortress of Despair with all their might, and swiftly decimated the many of the undead lurking within. After this devastating defeat, Vexana realized she needed to find a formidable ally, who could take on the Warrior of Light head on, or else she would face certain defeat. Vexana paced back and forth as she carefully pondered who had the strength to defeat Tigreal.</description></item><item><title>lesley</title><link>/hero/lesley.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/lesley.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LESLEY HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Lesley grew up in the Vance household, where her father presided over the noble family&amp;#39;s security. During an attack by a rival family, Lesley&amp;#39;s father was killed. As the assailants approached the Vance household, Lesley took up her father&amp;#39;s black long rifle and fulfilled her late father&amp;#39;s mission. Tears rolled down Lesley&amp;#39;s cheeks as she fired shot after shot, each one taking down an assassin.</description></item><item><title>ling</title><link>/hero/ling.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/ling.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LING HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; At the top of the mountains enshrouded by clouds, lies the entrance to the Hidden Land of the Dragon – the “Sky Arch”. Beside the Sky Arch stood many assassins in black. The cyan embroidery etched on their clothes identified them to being part of the most mysterious assassin faction of the Cadia Riverlands, the “Finch”. Legends say, it’s impossible to escape from claws of the “Finch”.</description></item><item><title>lolita</title><link>/hero/lolita.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/lolita.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LOLITA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Lolita was born in a distant elven village, living a happy, uneventful life. That is, until war brought an end to those peaceful, safe days. Her whole village was destroyed in the war; her family torn apart. Just as her own life was in grave peril, Rooney, the master machinist of the City of Scholars, found her when he was passing through and took her back to Eruditio.</description></item><item><title>lunox</title><link>/hero/lunox.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/lunox.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LUNOX HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; As the final battle started, the Twilight Orb devoured the energies within the Mage and opened, from which stepped out a girl, who was surrounded by the power of Chaos and Order. Her eyes are as deep as the ancient lake. The mysterious atmosphere she created then put all of the heroes into dreamland. The power of Chaos and Order have been struggling against each other since the ancient time, and the struggle had driven the world into desperation.</description></item><item><title>luoyi</title><link>/hero/luoyi.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/luoyi.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LUOYI HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; LUOYI MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Mage Lane: MID Lane Tier : A&amp;#43; Tier BP : 0 DM : 0 Ticket : 0 luoyi &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Luoyi Skills 1 &amp;times; Duality
Luo Yi's skills create marks of (Yin) and (Yang) on the battlefield, each lasting up to 6s. (Yin-Yang Reaction) happens whenever two bearers of opposite marks come close to each other, causing 400 (+15*Hero Level) ( +190% Total Magic Power) (Magic Damage) and stunning them for 1s.</description></item><item><title>lylia</title><link>/hero/lylia.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/lylia.html</guid><description>&amp;times; LYLIA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; At the underground lab of the Magic Academy, warnings and danger signs are everywhere. This is paradise for dark magicians. Sudden explosions and pungent magical potions make the place a horrible &amp;#34;Haunted House&amp;#34;. Few will come here, and no one is willing to befriend the dark magicians.The once brilliant black magicians are hard to find now. As a descendant of dark magicians, Lylia has a quirky character and unparallel magical creativity.</description></item><item><title>martis</title><link>/hero/martis.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/martis.html</guid><description>&amp;times; MARTIS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The Shura clan have thrived in isolation for countless generations, their men renowned for being the world&amp;#39;s bravest fighters, and their women famed for being the world&amp;#39;s greatest beauties. At the heart of the Shura clan&amp;#39;s beliefs lies the legend of the Three Thousand Worlds. The legend speaks of three thousand secret worlds, which upon entering, one must face various levels of psychic trials and advance to world after world upon victory.</description></item><item><title>masha</title><link>/hero/masha.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/masha.html</guid><description>&amp;times; MASHA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; There was a land in the far north called Northern Vale, which was covered by winter snow all year round. It was also known as the land closest to the Frozen Sea. In their long history, the Sarmi Tribe and the Bears shared their land. Having a common ancestor, they never attacked each other and lived in harmony. As time passed, they developed a spiritual bond.</description></item><item><title>mathilda</title><link>/hero/mathilda.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/mathilda.html</guid><description>&amp;times; MATHILDA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; MATHILDA MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Assassins Lane: ROAM Tier : S Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 mathilda &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Mathilda Skills 1 &amp;times; Ancestral Guidance
Mathilda gains (Ancestral Guidance) while moving. When it is fully charged, her next Basic Attack will be enhanced, dealing 160( +100% Total Physical ATK) ( +100% Total Magic Power) (Magic Damage) to the target and increasing her Movement Speed by 80 that will decay rapidly in 2.</description></item><item><title>minotaur</title><link>/hero/minotaur.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/minotaur.html</guid><description>&amp;times; MINOTAUR HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The labyrinth-dwelling Minotaur was once the symbol of power for the entire kingdom, up until he was defeated by a youth from a far-off land. In the many months and years since, he has trained alone in his labyrinth, hoping for the day when he might have a chance of defeating that young man. Time endowed the Minotaur with intelligence, and he learned how to concentrate his fury into more powerful explosions of strength.</description></item><item><title>minsitthar</title><link>/hero/minsitthar.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/minsitthar.html</guid><description>&amp;times; MINSITTHAR HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In the mysterious village of the East there was once a hero, &amp;#34;Holy Spear&amp;#34; Minsitthar, who had saved his kingdom from danger. He was once the Prince of Mahar Pura and served in the Forces from his youth. After adulthood he was respectfully called one of the &amp;#34;Four Great Generals&amp;#34; of Mahar Pura with his remarkable achievements. Minsitthar was invincible in wars, which earned the trust of the King and his people.</description></item><item><title>miya</title><link>/hero/miya.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/miya.html</guid><description>&amp;times; MIYA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Miya was born in the Temple of the Moon and studied hard to one day become a worthy sacrifice to the moon god. But when the fires of war of the race of men and orcs reached the moonlit shores of the moon elves&amp;#39; lakeside habitat, Miya rose up and led forth her countrymen in defiance of foreign invaders. Despite their best efforts, Miya and her fellow elves were finally forced by the countless enemy horde to make a last stand in the Temple of the Moon.</description></item><item><title>moskov</title><link>/hero/moskov.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/moskov.html</guid><description>&amp;times; MOSKOV HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Moskov, shooting to fame during the Dhamu Tournament, was already a battle master at his youth. He inherited the family&amp;#39;s occult spear fighting skills, and as the next leader of the clan Wildsand, he was loved and respected by many. Watching Wildsand clan growing stronger day by day, the khan of Thornwolf which is the hegemony on Hietala Grassland couldn&amp;#39;t sit back any longer.</description></item><item><title>nana</title><link>/hero/nana.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/nana.html</guid><description>&amp;times; NANA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Nana was born deep in a magic forest, and as a rare cat elf, she was naturally endowed with powerful but hard to control magic abilities. Periodic rages of magic outBurst nearly took out half of her forest home, until one day the journeying moon elf Miya restrained Nana and taught this young cat elf the secrets to controlling her magic abilities. The clever Nana quickly mastered these techniques, becoming a powerful cat elf mage.</description></item><item><title>natalia</title><link>/hero/natalia.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/natalia.html</guid><description>&amp;times; NATALIA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Natalia was raised from a little girl by the Church of Light and trained into one of the Church&amp;#39;s assassins. This young phenom had risen to become the top assassin for the Church via her outstanding talents, but then on one assassination mission, she failed, causing her companion to meet with unprecedented disaster. Although she was able to escape danger with Tigreal&amp;#39;s help, this was undoubtedly a severe blow to proud Natalia.</description></item><item><title>natan</title><link>/hero/natan.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/natan.html</guid><description> &amp;times; NATAN HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; NATAN MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Mage Lane: MID Lane Tier : Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 natan &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Natan Skills 1 &amp;times; Close Natan Skills 2 &amp;times; Close Natan Skills 3 &amp;times; Close Natan Skills 4 &amp;times; Close Build 1 (Generic) Other Build Build 2 (Generic) Other Build Rec Spell Rec Emblem Attributes Movement Speed &amp;nbsp;245 Physical Attack &amp;nbsp;110 Magic Power &amp;nbsp;0 Physical Defense &amp;nbsp;17 Magical Defense &amp;nbsp;15 HP &amp;nbsp;2530 Mana &amp;nbsp;443 Attack Speed &amp;nbsp; HP Regen &amp;nbsp;6 Mana Regen &amp;nbsp; Ability Offense ( 70% ) Durability ( 30% ) Ability ( 55% ) Difficulty ( 80% ) Contrary Hero Counter Hero</description></item><item><title>odette</title><link>/hero/odette.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/odette.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ODETTE HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; To the south of the Moniyan lies a sapphire like speck admist the misty mountains. It is in fact the Swan Lake, named after the beautiful yet authoritative Swan Castle that lies on the lake&amp;#39;s shores. Many years ago the Regina family fled from the empire&amp;#39;s capital to the lake in order to escape political conflicts and erected a Swan-like castle. According to legend that when Odette, the thirteenth generation scion was born, swans flocked to the castle to pay their respects.</description></item><item><title>paquito</title><link>/hero/paquito.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/paquito.html</guid><description>&amp;times; PAQUITO HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; PAQUITO MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Fighter Lane: EXP Lane Tier : S&amp;#43; Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 paquito &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Paquito Skills 1 &amp;times; Champ Stance
Paquito builds stacks when hitting enemy heroes with Basic Attacks or dealing damage with skills. Once this stack reaches 4, he enters (Champ Stance) and enhances his next skill.</description></item><item><title>pharsa</title><link>/hero/pharsa.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/pharsa.html</guid><description>&amp;times; PHARSA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The Crow people of Askati Forest are one of the oldest races to still exist in the Land of Dawn. This race was united by the Crow King Osana, under whose venerable leadership they perfected the art of Sky Magic.This unique school of magic allows its wielder to soar across the skies, and grants the ability to strike from enormous distances, however, only those who have had their blood &amp;#39;awakened&amp;#39; can use it.</description></item><item><title>phoveus</title><link>/hero/phoveus.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/phoveus.html</guid><description>&amp;times; PHOVEUS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; PHOVEUS MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Fighter Lane: EXP Lane Tier : S Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 phoveus &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Phoveus Skills 1 &amp;times; Demonic Intuition
Phoveus' weapon, (Astaros), holds mysterious powers and is exceptionally sensitive to fast-moving prey. When an enemy hero uses Blink or Charge skills within 8 yards of Astaros, it reduces all of Phoveus' skill cooldowns or charge times by 1s.</description></item><item><title>popol</title><link>/hero/popol.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/popol.html</guid><description>&amp;times; POPOL HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; POPOL MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Marksman Lane: Gold Lane Tier : A Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 popol &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Popol Skills 1 &amp;times; We Are Friends
Popol always fights side by side with his best partner, Kupa. Popol takes good care of Kupa. If Kupa hasn't taken any damage in 5s, 10% of its max HP will be restored each second.</description></item><item><title>rafaela</title><link>/hero/rafaela.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/rafaela.html</guid><description>&amp;times; RAFAELA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Rafaela is an angel capable of miraculously healing anything. It is said that when she appears, all pain suddenly vanishes, all wounds instantly heal, and all evil disperses like rain clouds when the sun comes out. Now Rafaela has descended upon the Land of Dawn in the hopes of using her miraculous powers to restore peace to the land. RAFAELA MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Supports Lane: ROAM Tier : S Tier BP : 6500 DM : 254 Ticket : 0 rafaela &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Rafaela Skills 1 &amp;times; Deity Penalization</description></item><item><title>roger</title><link>/hero/roger.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/roger.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ROGER HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Roger lives outside the dark forest to the east of the Megalith Wasteland. He is a hunter rich in experience who hunts for his livelihood. Many dangerous animals live in the dark forest, and the most fearsome among them aren&amp;#39;t rare magical creatures but the old wolf king &amp;#34;White Tooth&amp;#34; who leads a pack of wolves one hundred strong. They are cooperative pack hunters, and White Tooth also received the influence of an evil power that awakened magical abilities within him.</description></item><item><title>ruby</title><link>/hero/ruby.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/ruby.html</guid><description>&amp;times; RUBY HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; A long time ago, brave hunter grandpa saved Little Red Hood and her granny from the wolf&amp;#39;s belly and they lived happily ever after....though that was not how the real story ended. The wolf pack, harboring bitter resentment from this, never forgot the scars on the belly. One dark night when the moon was hidden, the new wolf king Haas led the pack and attacked the village in revenge, and elderly hunter grandpa was slained in an attempt to save granny.</description></item><item><title>saber</title><link>/hero/saber.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/saber.html</guid><description>&amp;times; SABER HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Scientists from another world gathered DNA from sword masters of hundreds of different races to create the ultimate swordsman using advanced technology. They named him Saber. His sword can tear a hole in spacetime, allowing him to travel to any place or time. His skills as a swordsman make him difficult to defeat, and also lonely beyond compare. After countless challengers were drawn to the land of dawn, Saber also turned his sights on this place, ripping through the fabric of space and time to set foot in the land of dawn and find an opponent worthy enough to face him.</description></item><item><title>selena</title><link>/hero/selena.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/selena.html</guid><description>&amp;times; SELENA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In the Southern Moniyan Empire, a bottomless abyss is carved into a barren landscape—As if a demon had used a powerful blade to permanently scar the Land of Dawn. The local populace call this place, the Shadow Abyss. Little does the world know, sealed away at the bottom of the Shadow Abyss lies the Land of Dawn&amp;#39;s most terrifying demon—The Abyss Dominator. Over the many centuries, the seal on the abyss has slowly faded, giving way to the hungry will of the Abyss.</description></item><item><title>silvanna</title><link>/hero/silvanna.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/silvanna.html</guid><description>&amp;times; SILVANNA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The prince has gone missing and no one knows if he&amp;#39;s dead or alive! For the sake of the country and the safety of its people, King Aurelius II has decreed to expand Knight&amp;#39;s Order and set up fortresses in the outskirts of Moniyan to reinforce the empire’s defense. In the meantime, Imperial Knights continue to search for any clue of the whereabouts of the prince.</description></item><item><title>sun</title><link>/hero/sun.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/sun.html</guid><description>&amp;times; SUN HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Sun, born from a rock, has been extraordinary since the very beginning. Long ago he was pinned down under a mountain by gods, trapped and unable to move. He watched time changing and watched the world being changed by the time. Although his body was covered by the freezing snow, the yearn for freedom in his heart never melted away. Waiting for the right opportunity to escape, he chanted &amp;#39;freedom&amp;#39; repeatedly and finally broke down his imprisonment, laughing as he flew away.</description></item><item><title>terizla</title><link>/hero/terizla.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/terizla.html</guid><description>&amp;times; TERIZLA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; If belief could bring love, hope, and salvation to the world, then how come there are still hurt souls lingering about?&amp;#34; - a saying carved on the stela of the Monastery of Light in the Moniyan Empire. Deep in the Monastery stands an iron cage, called &amp;#34;the door to rebirth.&amp;#34; Within this cage, hides the dark and secret history of the Empire. TERIZLA MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Fighter Lane: EXP Lane Tier : C Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 terizla &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Terizla Skills 1 &amp;times; Body of Smith</description></item><item><title>thamuz</title><link>/hero/thamuz.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/thamuz.html</guid><description>&amp;times; THAMUZ HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Deep within the mountains, darkness reigns over everything. The only light is the crimson lava that flows in the bottomless crevices. Since the beginning of the abyss&amp;#39;s reign on the mainland, countless demons became loyal followers of the Abyss. Fervent in their beliefs, the demons chant the will of the Abyss in these deep caverns — Only the strong deserve to rule! Guarding the Abyss for millenniums, a tribe of fire demons nearly became the rulers of the Abyss.</description></item><item><title>tigreal</title><link>/hero/tigreal.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/tigreal.html</guid><description>&amp;times; TIGREAL HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In every battle, the mystic warrior Tigreal always fought in the front line and never suffered defeat. Even the vilest of enemies did not dare to challenge Tigreal on the battlefield, because they knew such a foolish action would only be met with Tigreal&amp;#39;s merciless blade. The name of Tigreal, a believer in the Lord of Light, has become synonymous with bravery and fearlessness.</description></item><item><title>uranus</title><link>/hero/uranus.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/uranus.html</guid><description>&amp;times; URANUS HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; The Celestial Palace - Legend has it that this city floating above the skies of the Land of Dawn was once home to the gods. It is also said that this mysterious place holds the key to ruling the world… Eons ago, the ruler of the Celestial Palace used the technological secrets of the ancients to create Uranus, and commanded his creation to guard the city and wait for the emergence of a new ruler.</description></item><item><title>vale</title><link>/hero/vale.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/vale.html</guid><description>&amp;times; VALE HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; &amp;#34;Valir, my beloved brother. You lost everything the day we made The Pact. I’ll see to it that the Fire Kingdom restores everything to the way it once was. If you wish to avenge your cruel father, I do not blame you as long as you can cast away the storm within your heart. Nothing is as important as your happiness, not even my life.</description></item><item><title>valir</title><link>/hero/valir.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/valir.html</guid><description>&amp;times; VALIR HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Legend has it, that at the end of the western desert, there lies a beautiful and rich country. This fabled land is where Valir is from. From his very first day at the magic academy, Valir&amp;#39; extraordinary control over the arcane was clear for all to see. Gord, who was teaching arcane arts at the time, saw a little of himself in Valir, and began to teach the most coveted secrets of the arcane to his inquisitive pupil.</description></item><item><title>vexana</title><link>/hero/vexana.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/vexana.html</guid><description>&amp;times; VEXANA HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; A long, long time ago, there was a small country with a kind and caring king and queen, held in high esteem by their subjects. Under the protection of the god of light, they lived a peaceful life. But deep under the ground, a lord of the dark abyss was plotting to invade their land. The Dark Lord sent the enchanting vampire queen Alice to tempt the king.</description></item><item><title>wanwan</title><link>/hero/wanwan.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/wanwan.html</guid><description>&amp;times; WANWAN HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; In the south of the Cadia Riverlands lies a picturesque land where the civilization of Ba and Shu lived. “The Land of Abundance” was what the natives called this place. Tangmen, a faction that was known for their hidden weapons and skilled craft, originated from this land. However, Tangmen’s new leader found that many people often used Tangmen’s crafts and hidden weapons to do evil, which was running against his will.</description></item><item><title>xborg</title><link>/hero/xborg.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/xborg.html</guid><description>&amp;times; XBORG HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Extraordinary intelligence has the ability to lead the world into a new light or make some major changes for the worse. It&amp;#39;s a priceless treasure, even when based on countless failures. For overwhelming technology, people are willing to sacrifice a great deal. The Eruditio, located in the north-west of the Land of Dawn, was the symbol of the highest intelligence. They made all that was impossible possible.</description></item><item><title>yisunshin</title><link>/hero/yisunshin.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/yisunshin.html</guid><description>&amp;times; YISUNSHIN HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Chungmugong Yi Sun-shin was a famous general in an Asian kingdom. He was extremely loyal and of prowess. At the time when the nation was in danger, Yi Sun-shin built a powerful navy and created the iron armored &amp;#39;turtle ship&amp;#39;, making indelible contribution to Korea Kingdom for dominating around sea areas. &amp;#39;Wherever iron turtle ships sail on, the sea areas belong to me.&amp;#39; said Yi.</description></item><item><title>yuzhong</title><link>/hero/yuzhong.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/yuzhong.html</guid><description>&amp;times; YUZHONG HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; YUZHONG MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Fighter Lane: EXP Lane Tier : A Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : yuzhong &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Yuzhong Skills 1 &amp;times; Cursing Touch
Yu Zhong applies (Sha Residue) to the target every time he deals damage to enemy heroes, and gathers (Sha Essence) in the meantime. (Sha Residue) erupts upon reaching 5 stacks, consuming 1 stack every 0.</description></item><item><title>yve</title><link>/hero/yve.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/yve.html</guid><description>&amp;times; YVE HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; YVE MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Mage Lane: MID Lane Tier : A&amp;#43; Tier BP : 32000 DM : 599 Ticket : 0 yve &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Yve Skills 1 &amp;times; Void Blast
Yve detonates Galactic Energy in a designated area, dealing 180( +80% Total Magic Power) (Magic Damage) to the targets. The targets in the central area will take an extra 180( +80% Total Magic Power) (Magic Damage).</description></item><item><title>zhask</title><link>/hero/zhask.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/zhask.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ZHASK HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; A great civilization rose out of the ashes of history, but the aggressive nature of the Kastiyans have persisted to the present. Kastiyans use their time space warping and psionic mind abilities to vanquish weaker races at pleasure. After countless generations of evolution, the Kastiyans have been able to fully mentally manipulate the insect spirit &amp;#34;Domorey&amp;#34;, or the &amp;#39;nightmaric spawn&amp;#39; as they call her in the Kastiyan language.</description></item><item><title>zilong</title><link>/hero/zilong.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/zilong.html</guid><description>&amp;times; ZILONG HD Wallpaper &amp;#10094; &amp;#10095; Zilong is a son of the Great Dragon, sworn to roam from world to world assisting wise rulers by the Dragon&amp;#39;s decree. Whenever a new king is in need of strength, Zilong traverses space and time to remove all obstacles and enemies before the king using spear fighting techniques endowed upon him by the Great Dragon. ZILONG MOBILE LEGENDS Role: Fighter Lane: EXP Lane Tier : A&amp;#43; Tier BP : 0 DM : 0 Ticket : 0 zilong &amp;times; @ Close More Info Hero skills Zilong Skills 1 &amp;times; Dragon Flurry</description></item></channel></rss>