<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chou on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/chou.html</link><description>Recent content in Chou on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/chou/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>chou</title><link>/hero/chou.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/chou.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">CHOU HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/chou.jpg" title="CHOU HD Wallpaper" alt="CHOU HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> Chou was born in a secluded slum deep in the hearts of poverty, living the lowest quality of life. Despite the dreadful conditions Chou still kept his heart of kindness, as day in day out he continued to look after the old and the young there with passion. At that time, there was great turmoil and unrest in the Land of the Dawn; mayhem spread throughout the land and eventually started to affect this small remote area. One day, Chou rescued a mystic monk under pursuit by his captors, and took him back to his slum to care for him. In return, the monk imparted the ancient Asian Kung-Fu skill to Chou, and told him that the world needed a real hero to stand up and end the turmoils. Chou made a vow right there and then, and without looking back he would start out on his journey in the Land to become a true hero. As Chou was leaving, the monk nodded and disappeared into the shadows. &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>