<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hanabi on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/hanabi.html</link><description>Recent content in Hanabi on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/hanabi/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>hanabi</title><link>/hero/hanabi.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/hanabi.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">HANABI HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/hanabi.jpg" title="HANABI HD Wallpaper" alt="HANABI HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> Hanabi received the teachings of the Scarlet Shadow ninja sect&amp;#39;s Supreme Grandmaster from a young age, exhibiting natural talent that far exceeded any of her peers, until she met a young shadow ninja called Hayabusa. This was the very first time the proud Hanabi came across anyone who could hold their own against her. Whenever the moon was full, Hanabi would try to find ways to provoke this young shadow ninja into dueling with her, however, she could never defeat this youngster, who fused spiritualism with shadow techniques to create a unique and powerful style. As the two of them slowly grew up together, it began to dawn on Hanabi that this young shadow ninja carried the burden of an inescapable fate -- Hayabusa was in fact destined to challenge and kill the legendary former Shadow of Iga for his betrayal of their clan. After the two young ninjas fought, Hayabusa would lie on the ground, staring up at the full moon in the sky, the reflection of the moonlight in his eyes quietly burning into Hanabi&amp;#39;s heart. Having never felt this kind of feeling before, Hanabi became very distressed. Whenever she saw Hayabusa and the young spiritualist girl known as Kagura smiling and laughing as they greeted each other, her heart would fill with inexplicable rage and vexation. When she heard that Hayabusa would become the clan&amp;#39;s next Shadow, she decided to take on the name Scarlet, and from the secret vault of the Supreme Grandmaster, she stole her sect&amp;#39;s forbidden weapon - the Higanbana. Hanabi decided that she would challenge her age-old rival to one final competition, and now her one aim in life is to find and kill the disgraced former Shadow before Hayabusa does. &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>