<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Helcurt on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/helcurt.html</link><description>Recent content in Helcurt on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/helcurt/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>helcurt</title><link>/hero/helcurt.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/helcurt.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">HELCURT HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/helcurt.jpg" title="HELCURT HD Wallpaper" alt="HELCURT HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> In the museum records of the Lord of Dawn, there is said to be a mysterious race that once forged a great empire. This race was blessed with the power to swallow up light, for they are able to temporarily blackout a space. This was not the only talent they possessed, as they also had the ability to blink through physical space, being able to surprise enemies for a sneak attack. What’s most terrifying about them, however, is what was on their tails, a concoction of naturally sourced poison, for those unfortunate enough to come in contact with the poison would should say their last words, but ultimately this is also what caused the demise of their very own race. In the annals, it does not give the specifics on how this race went extinct, but it is certain that this terrifying race definitely did walk upon on the Land of Dawn. Since their extinction, humanity had progressed prosperously, however, but the history books could not predict that one day these creatures would slowly creep out of the shadows again... &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>