<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Martis on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/martis.html</link><description>Recent content in Martis on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/martis/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>martis</title><link>/hero/martis.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/martis.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">MARTIS HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/martis.jpg" title="MARTIS HD Wallpaper" alt="MARTIS HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> The Shura clan have thrived in isolation for countless generations, their men renowned for being the world&amp;#39;s bravest fighters, and their women famed for being the world&amp;#39;s greatest beauties. At the heart of the Shura clan&amp;#39;s beliefs lies the legend of the Three Thousand Worlds. The legend speaks of three thousand secret worlds, which upon entering, one must face various levels of psychic trials and advance to world after world upon victory. The people of the Shura clan have discovered a way to enter these worlds, and only those who have conquered over three hundred worlds are granted the title of &amp;#34;Ashura&amp;#34;, raising them to the level of a demigod in the eyes of their people. However, in the innumerable eons of Shura history, none managed to conquer the fabled three thousand worlds, until Martis appeared. With ambition and determination capable of shaking the very heavens, Martis trained every day of his life to become stronger, tirelessly advancing through the secret worlds, each personal breakthrough against the legions of demons granting him a sense of unique personal satisfaction. No one knows how many years passed before Martis reached the final secret world, but his desire for glory drove him onwards. After numerous defeats, he fell into despair, but even then, he refused to give up. He transformed his sheer thirst for victory into twin blades of righteous fury, now known as the Ashura&amp;#39;s Teeth, and for countless days and nights, battled against the demons of the final world with strength and determination never seen before on the mortal plane. He finally became the first Ashura to defeat the three thousand secret worlds and has since been regarded as &amp;#39;King Ashura&amp;#39;, ruling tens of millions of aspiring Ashura. &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>