<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Odette on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/odette.html</link><description>Recent content in Odette on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/odette/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>odette</title><link>/hero/odette.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/odette.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">ODETTE HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/odette.jpg" title="ODETTE HD Wallpaper" alt="ODETTE HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> To the south of the Moniyan lies a sapphire like speck admist the misty mountains. It is in fact the Swan Lake, named after the beautiful yet authoritative Swan Castle that lies on the lake&amp;#39;s shores. Many years ago the Regina family fled from the empire&amp;#39;s capital to the lake in order to escape political conflicts and erected a Swan-like castle. According to legend that when Odette, the thirteenth generation scion was born, swans flocked to the castle to pay their respects. Princess Odette is said to have a contagious smile, leading people to say she is a goddess in human form. In order to match the praise that people have piled on her, Windor mastered the most difficult of noble magics. Despite being universally admired, Odette had been lonely at heart until chance brought her to Lancelot, whose wounds had led him to faint on the lakeshore. During Lancelot&amp;#39;s recovery, the two soon developed a deep unconditional love. &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>