<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Belerick on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/belerick.html</link><description>Recent content in Belerick on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/belerick/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>belerick</title><link>/hero/belerick.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/belerick.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">BELERICK HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/belerick.jpg" title="BELERICK HD Wallpaper" alt="BELERICK HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> Legends say, the Ancient Ones of the Land of Dawn trusted mystical creatures with grand tasks. ########Belerick, a member of the tree people, was one of this creatures. Belerick’s heart is filled with nothing but kindness—He absolutely hates conflict. Within his ancient self, Belerick possesses a strong life force that provides strong resistance against a attacks, but also allows him to reincarnate. Due to his kind nature, wherever there is conflcit, Belerick will be there to help the righteous and weak. ########One day, Belerick believed he heard the words of the ancient ones guiding him towards the desert. However, he was met with disaster. The great Minoan empire was left in ruins and Minotaur people were filled with despair. In order to save what was left of the Minoans, Belerick unleashed all of his life force to create a beautiful oasis. The Minoan people were filled with hope once more. Seeing this, Belerick’s heart was at peace and fell into a deep slumber. Although Belerick can not pursue the task the Ancient Ones bestowed upon him, he felt no regret—There’s nothing more important than life after all. &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>