<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Harith on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</title><link>/categories/harith.html</link><description>Recent content in Harith on Build - MobaGenie - Mobile Legends Build Guide</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/categories/harith/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>harith</title><link>/hero/harith.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hero/harith.html</guid><description>&lt;div id="ModalHero" class="modal2">
 &lt;span class="close cursor" onclick="closeModal()">&amp;times;&lt;/span>
 &lt;div class="modal-content">

 &lt;div class="mySlidesHero">
 &lt;div class="numbertext">HARITH HD Wallpaper&lt;/div>
 &lt;img src="https://res.cloudinary.com/drlhixyyd/image/fetch/c_fill,g_face,f_auto/https://cdn2-build.mobagenie.my.id/p/images/banner/full/harith.jpg" title="HARITH HD Wallpaper" alt="HARITH HD Wallpaper" style="width:100%">	
 &lt;/div>

 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 &lt;a class="prev" onclick="plusSlides(-1)">&amp;#10094;&lt;/a>
 &lt;a class="next" onclick="plusSlides(1)">&amp;#10095;&lt;/a>

 &lt;div class="caption-container">
 &lt;p id="caption">
	 &lt;div> In the Magic Forest lives the race of gremlins. They&amp;#39;re small, naughty creatures with high intelligence and independent traits. They have been the most faithful ally to the Moon Elf since the history begins. Harith was born with outstanding mind, he soon became the best wizard among the Feline Race. The Feline People are a peaceful kind that seeks tranquility. They have never stepped out of the Magic Forest once. But Harith is troubled by the peaceful life to the point that he had once abandoned practicing magic. His inner desire for transcendence drove him out of the Magic Forest and he went to the Empire Moniyan, in a bid to find a place where his talent can be fully revealed. He joined the Imperial Troop and became a rising star in the battles against the Orc invaders, thus he was recognized by Tigreal and the Emperor. Harith was loved by the Moniyan people. As a Feline person, he was nominated the Magic Lieutenant and the Imperial Wizard of Seal. He was also given the power to keep the Key of Light, which has the power to teleport things. The young Magic Lieutenant was then assigned to seal the evil powers marked on the Imperial Scroll. The desire for adventure was again ignited in Harith&amp;#39;s heart. Though he knew he will be targeted as the Wizard of Seal, he still chose to burden the destiny of suffering nostalgia and dangers. He acts in a mysterious way that no one could find the trace of him, but whenever the Empire needs help, the Wizard of Seal shows up. &lt;/div>
	 &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>